（ヤサコ）都市伝説によると
According to urban legends,
メガネをかけたまま眠って
夢の中で―
kids that have fallen asleep with their cyberglasses on
have ended up going to the "other side".
あっちに入り込んでしまった
子供がいたそうです
（ヤサコ）ここ 前にも来たわ
I've been here before...
（少年）ユウコ…
Yuko...
（少年）ユウコ 気をつけろ…
Be careful.
Yuko...
すぐ近くにいる
You're very close to it.
待って！　あなたは何？
Wait! Who are you?
（少年）逃げろ
Run away.
（ヤサコ）
４４２３って なんなの？
What does 4-4-2-3 mean?
（少年）ユウコ 逃げるんだ
Yuko,
you must run away!
早く…
Hurry!
待って！
Wait!
わあー！
ハァ… 夢か
A dream?
（ウチクネ）おらおら
遅刻すんぞー！
C'mon, c'mon! You're gonna be late!
The Summer Festival
and the Duel
（フミエ）ヤサコ！
（ヤサコ）おはよう
Yasako!
Good morning.
１学期 最後の日に
遅刻するところだった
I was almost late on the last day of the term!
こら お前！
こんな所で何やっとる…
Hey, ya jerk!
What the hell are ya doin'...
…んですか？
...here?
（ハラケン）
オバちゃん 助かったよ
You're a lifesaver, auntie.
（２人）ハラケン！
Haraken!
Thank you.
ありがとう
（オバちゃん）
んもう～ ケンちゃんのためなら
なんでもやるわ
You know I'd do anything for you.
あっ… やめてよ
Cut it out!
（オバちゃん）ちょっと そこの！
（ウチクネ）はい！
Hey, you there!
Yes?
（オバちゃん）駐車場は どこ？
（ウチクネ）あ… あちらです
Where's the parking lot?
Uh, it's, err... over there.
（ダイチ）イサコさん
これが昨日の上がりです
Miss Isako!
These are yesterday's profits.
（ナメッチ）おお～！
（ダイチ）さすがイサコさん
Amazing, Miss Isako!
（イサコ）
その“イサコさん”っていうの
やめてくれる？
Would you stop calling me Isako?
（ダイチ）ところで
これも献上したいのですが
By the way, I'd like to give you this.
今夜の夏祭りの
プラチナチケットです
It's a platinum ticket for tonight's summer festival!
なんすか それ？
（ダイチ）知らんのか？
What's that?
You don't know?
金魚すくいから射的まで
あらゆる縁日がタダになる―
This is a superticket that allows you to try
any of the attractions for free, from the red fish fishing to the shooting range!
スーパーチケットなのだ
That's really...
それは… すごいっすね
amazing.
（カンナ）今日も交差点で見たの
研一(けんいち)は信じないけど…
I saw it again today at the crossing.
Maybe you won't believe me, Ken'ichi,
やっぱり あれはクロエだと思う
but yeah,
I think it was Kuroe.
明日 どうしても
一緒に見に行ってほしいの
I really need you to go there tomorrow and see for yourself.
どうかな？
Can you do that?
鹿屋野(かやの)神社で待ってます
Meet you at Kayano Shrine.
（オバちゃん）
こっちの子は天沢(あまさわ)勇子(ゆうこ)
So this girl is Yuko Amasawa.
ふむ 引っ越してきて２週間か
She moved into town two weeks ago.
あちこち荒らす時間は十分ね
More than enough time to cause trouble all over.
And here's the other one.
もう１人は こっち
Well then,
さて 駅ビルに穴を開けたのは
どっちかしらね？
I wonder which one opened
the hole in the station.
I knew it.
（イサコ）やはり 古い空間がある
There's an obsolete Space here.
わりと広いわ
It's pretty big.
確認する
I'll go verify.
もう１人の…
これも転校したばかりか
This one
moved here recently too.
Isn't that the same surname as my boss?
うちの室長と同じ名字
Oh man! She's the boss' daughter!
あちゃ～ ボスの娘だ
Things are getting complex.
ややこしくなってきた
Pochi,
ポチ 今のはキラバグ反応か？
was that a kirabug signal?
I better put out more of these just in case.
念のために もっと仕掛けておくか
A-And you are...?
（マイコ）ど… どちら様？
Oh my, if it isn't Maiko-sensei!
あっ あらヤダ！　マイコ先生
I'm Miss Harakawa!
原川(はらかわ)です
Um...
（マイコ）えっと…
ああ 生物部の原川君の？
Ah!
The relative of Harakawa from the Biology Club?
Yes, that's right!
はい そうです そうです
前に一度 お会いしたことが…
We've met before.
Oh...
（マイコ）
あっ アハハ… その節は
from that time!
I'm really sorry I drank too much;
私 飲みすぎちゃって
お恥ずかしいところを…
I'm so embarrassed!
（オバちゃん）
とんでもございません
That's all right.
By the way, I'm actually on the clock.
ところで わたくし
今 勤務中でして
I was tracking an abnormality in the Space,
空間の乱れをたどってきたら
and there seem to be some irregularities in the gym.
どうやら
体育館の中が怪しいようです
Could you please show me around?
案内してもらえますか？
Oh...
in that case...
あっ じゃあ
こちらに どうぞ
Well, please follow me.
One false move and she'll be on to me.
うかつに動かすと
あいつに気づかれるわね
Should I create a diversion?
陽動で行くか
In the last two years,
（教頭）
去年のように 皆さん自身が―
a number of you kids have become at risk of causing car accidents.
事故の原因になってしまうことも
あります
特にメガネに夢中の人
Please don't use your glasses
when you go out in the street.
道路では
メガネを使用しないように…
Geez!
ヤダわ
またメガネのせいにして
He's blaming the glasses again.
Hey, Fumie.
（ヤサコ）ねえ フミエちゃん
（フミエ）んっ？
Do you think the teachers feel the same way?
（ヤサコ）先生たちも
あんなふうに思ってるのね
What's that?
何が？
That Kanna's death was her own fault.
事故の原因が
カンナさんの不注意だって
I think they do.
ああ そうよね
Haraken has suffered for a year all alone.
（ヤサコ）ハラケン
１年も１人で苦しんでたのよ
Now I know why he's always so gloomy.
（フミエ）
なんで ずっと暗かったのか
よく分かったわよね
Me too...
ホントねえ
頑張って ハラケンの研究を
手伝いましょう
Let's do our best to help out with Haraken's research!
こっちがボスの娘
This one is the boss' daughter.
そして もう１人は…
And the other one...
あのオバちゃん
終業式まで なんの用よ
That old lady...
She came to the closing ceremony. What's she up to?
んっ？　どうしたの？
What is it?
（ヤサコ）それが 聞いたら―
Well, I asked my dad about her,
あの人 どうやら
お父さんの部下らしいの
and if I'm not mistaken, she's an employee from his department.
Huh?
お父さん メガマスって
メガネの会社に勤めてるの
You know, my father works for the glasses company, Megamass.
今は市役所に出向してるんだって
As far as I know, he's temporarily working at the municipal office.
へえー すごい奇遇ね
What an amazing coincidence!
んっ？　じゃあ あのダサい
サッチーのネーミングって…
So that ridiculous nickname, "Satchii"...
お父さんが考えたらしいわ
...was apparently my dad's choice.
“ボク サッチー”ってのもね
The same goes for the "Me Satchii!" thing.
そ… そうなの
R-Really?
あっ 見て ヤサコ
（ヤサコ）えっ？
Oh, look over there, Yasako.
（フミエ）
あの人がカンナのお母さんよ
That lady is Kanna's mother.
（教師）はい　皆さん 静かに
Okay, kids! Quiet please.
（カンナの母）ケンちゃん
Ken.
（ハラケン）おばさん
Ma'am.
（カンナの母）
久しぶりね ケンちゃん
It's been a long time, Ken.
具合はどう？　立ちくらみ
How are you doing?
How are your dizzy spells?
（ハラケン）大丈夫です
あの頃に１～２度あっただけだから
I'm all right now.
I've only had them a couple of times since then.
おばさん 警察は
結局 なんて言ってきたの？
Ma'am,
what did the police say in their report?
電脳ナビだから
過失はありえないって
They said the cybernavi couldn't have made a mistake.
むしろ カンナのほうに―
On the contrary,
何か原因があったんじゃないかって
言ってたわ
they believe Kanna was somehow the cause.
今度 この町を離れることにしたの
I've decided to leave this town.
そうだ それでね
最後にケンちゃんにお願いがあるの
By the way,
there's something I'd like to ask you.
カンナのメガネよ
These are Kanna's glasses.
やっと警察から戻ってきて
The police finally returned them.
中を調べたかったんだけど
鍵がかかってるみたいなの
I wanted to look inside,
but they must require some sort of key.
この中に私たちに宛てた何か
残ってないか調べてほしいの
I'd like you to find out
if there're any clues inside that might prove useful to us.
いいの？
Can I?
（カンナの母）他人に頼むより
ケンちゃんに見てもらうほうが
I'm sure that Kanna
would be more at ease if it were you
カンナも きっと安心だと思うの
and not some stranger that looked into it.
（ハラケン）うん 分かった
I understand.
カンナが
なぜ あの日 あそこにいて
Why Kanna was there that day,
何をしていたのか
どんな気持ちだったのか
what she was doing,
what she was feeling.
それだけが知りたいの
That's all I want to know.
おばさん 待ってて
Ma'am, please wait for me.
僕 きっと真相を突き止めて
おばさんに伝えるよ
I'll find out the truth behind this for sure,
and report it to you, ma'am.
（アイコ）
ねえ もしかしてさ ヤサコ
ハラケンに気があったりして
Hey, could it be
that Yasako feels something for Haraken?
えっ そう？
You think so?
（ダイチ）♪ 夏祭り アソレ～
Sum-mer fes-ti-val! Oh yeah!
Today's a fun, fun sum-mer fes-ti-val...
元オヤビン
踊ってないで手伝ってくださいよ
Hey, ex-boss!
Stop dancing around and help us out!
（ガチャギリ）
そうだぜ 元リーダー
He's right, ex-leader!
早く仕込まねえと終わらねえぞ
We have to finish, or we won't be done on time!
“元 元”言うな！
仕込みは ほとんど終わってんだ
Stop calling me "ex"!
We're almost done training!
祭りの準備 行こうぜ
Now let's get ready for the festival!
（イサコ）まだよ
Not yet.
（ナメッチ）オ… オヤビン！
B-Boss!
（ガチャギリ）
まだって… なんでだ？
Not yet?
（イサコ）
念のために向こうの校舎にも
ショートカットを仕掛けるのよ
Just in case, we'll set a shortcut to the other school building, too.
俺 夏祭りの準備もあるんすよ
Hey, I have to get ready for the festival...
（ガチャギリ）
そもそも なんのために
こんなことさせんだよ
And besides, what do you want us to do all this stuff for?
合宿の夜
あの連中を果たし合いと称して
On the night of the school sleepover,
you'll have a duel against them,
校舎の中に おびき出しなさい
and then you'll lure them inside the school building.
それに勝って
あいつらのメガネを取り上げるのよ
After you defeat them, you'll take their glasses.
詳細は そこに書いてあるわ
The details are written in there.
Duel?
果たし合い？
こんな子供っぽいこと
やってられっかよ！
Hey, we can't go around doing such childish things!
こっちだって忙しいんだ
We don't have time for that!
また逆らうのか？
Are you disobeying me again?
ま… 待て！　逆らう気はねえよ
W-Wait...
We don't mean to disobey.
（デンパ）そ… そうだよ
そうだよね？　ダイチ
Th-That's right.
Isn't that right, Daichi?
Then do as I say.
なら 言うとおりにしろ
何度も言わせるな！
Don't make me repeat myself!
（一同）へ～い
（イサコ）ダイチ君
（ダイチ）な… なんだよ
Daichi.
What is it?
You asked to become my disciple, did you not?
あんた
私に弟子にしてくださいって
言ったわよね
If you succeed in this plan,
この作戦がうまくいったら
いくつか暗号屋の技を
教えてあげるわ
I'll teach you a few encoding techniques.
本当か？
Really?!
Really.
本当よ
でも もし失敗したら
大黒黒客(だいこくヘイクー)から追放よ
But if you fail...
You'll be dismissed from this club.
何？
What?!
ったくよ… ムカつくぜ 女のくせに
What the hell?
She pisses me off!
And she's just a girl!
俺のクラブだぜ
俺を追い出せるわけねえだろ
This is my club!
How could she possibly dismiss me?
（ガチャギリ）逆らえねえよ
とっとと終わらせようぜ
We can't go against her.
Just a little more and we're done.
（ダイチ）
おまいら 俺の代わりやっとけ
I'll let you guys take care of my part.
（アキラ）えっ？
（デンパ）ズルいよ ダイチ！
You're so mean, Daichi!
（ダイチ）町内会長の息子が―
I'm the son of the festival's committee president,
how can I possibly skip helping with the preparations?
祭りの準備をサボるわけには
いかねえんだよ
You just want to skip work, don't you?
こっちをサボりたいだけだろ！
祭りがそんなに大事なのかよ
Is that festival so important?
おめえらには分かるめえよ
江戸っ子の心意気ってもんがな
You just don't get it.
It's called "the spirit of a Tokyo kid".
But he dresses and acts like a Daikoku kid.
（ナメッチ）
生まれも育ちも大黒市のくせして
（ハラケン）
やっぱり クロエの病気のことを
調べようとしたんだな
So she was really looking into Kuroe's sickness...
Locked
お母さん
この辺 よく知ってるのよね？
Mom, you know this town really well, right?
Yes,
（静江(しずえ)）うん 駅のこっち側なら
お父さんとよく歩いたわ
I used to take many walks side-by-side near the station with your father.
Way back before you were born.
ユウちゃんが生まれる前
Is there a stairway with a lot of torii on it?
ねえ 鳥居がいっぱい並んでる
階段ってない？
A stairway?
（静江）
階段？　さあ… 知らないな
Well, I don't know.
Look, they've started!
おおー やってる やってる
Hey, you're finally here!
（ダイチ）おっ おまいら来たか！
（一同）んっ？
Come over here!
こっち こっち！　まあ 上がれ
C'mon, climb!
So this is the plan:
計画としては こうだ
Tomorrow, at the school sleepover, we'll challenge Busue and her gang to a trial of courage.
明日の合宿で
ブスエどもを肝試しに招待する
Of course, I've laid lots traps on the course.
もちろん コースには
ワナをたっぷり仕掛けてな
Then we'll focus our attack,
そして 集中攻撃して―
and make her pay for the two years' otoshidama damage she did!
お年玉２年分の損害を
食らわせてやるのだ
Well, it's exactly as the boss, Isako, said to do.
まあ イサコオヤビンの
計画のまんまっすね
Shut up!
うっさいな！
Okay, now, let's follow the plan.
さあ 予定どおり行くぞ
Oh, now I remember, Isako said...
あっ そうだ イサコが…
（ダイチ）なんだよ
Said what?
...that we'd better wait until she arrives.
“やっぱり
私が行くまで待ってろ”って
なんで？
Why?
She said she doesn't feel comfortable leaving everything to you.
お前一人じゃ
安心できないそうだ
What the hell! That...!
なんだと？　あんにゃろう！
ナメやがって…
She's looking down on me!
（ダイチの父）こら ダイチ！
（ダイチ）イテテテ…
Hey, Daichi!
How dare you skip helping out today?
遅刻したうえにサボりおって！
C'mere!
（ダイチの父）来い！
（ダイチ）痛い！　離して 親父(おやじ)！
It hurts!
Let go of me, Dad!
Please Enter Your Password
オバさんが言ってた
“鍵がかかってる”って
So this is the key Kanna's mother mentioned.
これのことだな
Invalid
（ヤサコ）ハラケン
Haraken.
ごめんね 遅れちゃって
Sorry for being late.
（ヤサコ）どうしたの？
What's wrong?
あっ フ… フミエは？
Where's Fumie?
（ヤサコ）
まだよ ちょっと遅刻するって
She's not here yet.
She said she'd be a little late.
（京子(きょうこ)）ふっ！
（ダイチ）アイタッ
Ow!
何しやがんだ！　このジャリ
What the hell are you doing with those rocks?!
ダイチ君 ここで何してるの？
Daichi, what are you doing here?
お前らに
果たし合いを申し渡しにきた
I came here to challenge you to a duel.
は… 果たし合い？
A d-duel?
そうだ！
えっと… フミエはどこだ？
That's right!
So where's Fumie?
（ヤサコ）まだ来てないの
She's not here yet.
そうか では待つ
I see.
Then I'll wait for her.
イテッ！
Ow!
（京子）ブンブ～ン！
（ヤサコ）京子！
Kyoko!
（ヤサコ）
ねえ 立ってるのも疲れるから
ラムネでも買わない？
It's going to be boring if we just stand here like this; let's buy some ramune.
おっ いいね… じゃない
Oh, great idea!
I mean...
ま… まあ いいだろう
Well, it's okay. I guess.
ななな… 何すんだ この！
（京子）ブンブ～ン！
What the hell are you doing, you brat?!
京子 変な人に近づいちゃいけない
って言ったでしょ
Kyoko!
I've told you not to get close to strangers, haven't I?
叱り方が違うだろ！
That's not what you should be scolding her for!
（フミエ）お待たせ！
（ヤサコ）あっ
Sorry to keep you waiting!
ようやく現れやがったな…
So you finally came out from under your rock, you damn...
（フミエ）
ごめんね 遅刻しちゃって
Sorry.
I'm late. I—
うわっ ダイチ！
Daichi!
何よ！　なんで あんた
こんな所にいるの？
What do you want?
What are you doing here?
だって 俺は… 町内会だから
Well, you see,
I'm on the town committee...
ああ そうだったわね
Oh, now I remember.
んっ？　あんた
なんで濡(ぬ)れてんの？
Hey, why are you all wet?
ハッ！　お漏らし？
Did you just...?
（ヤサコ）ダイチ君
何か言うことがあるみたいよ
I think Daichi has something to tell you.
（フミエ）はあ？　こんな日にまで
なんのイヤがらせよ
So what nastiness are you planning to spoil my day?
い… 一緒に
サッカーやりませんか？
D-Do you wanna play soccer with me?
違うな
That's not right...
い… 一緒に
ザリガニ釣り行きませんか？
D-Do you wanna catch crayfish with me?
ち… 違うな
No, that's not it...
あっ そうだ
Oh, I know!
い… 一緒に
Would you...
夏祭り行きませんか？
come with me to the summer festival?
Would...
Huh?
（ダイチ）一緒に…
Would you come to a duel with me?
果たし合いに行きませんか？
ったく… 何やってんだ
What the heck are you doing?
How could you challenge her before Isako showed up?
イサコが来る前に
挑戦しちゃうヤツがあるかよ
There's still thirty minutes left.
（アキラ）あと30分ありますね
ぶはっ… うるへえ！
Shut up!
そんな回りくどいこと
やってられっかよ
I'd never use such an indirect approach!
I wrung out your jacket.
（デンパ）はっぴ絞ったよ
（フミエ･ヤサコ）フフフフ…
D-Don't look!
み… 見るな！
I dunno know what she's going to say about this...
あの女 何言うか分かんねえからな
Just wait thirty minutes, then ask her again.
30分たったら
もう１回 申し込めよ
実はね もう情報はつかんでたのよ
果たし合いの
To tell you the truth, I already knew about it.
About the duel.
えっ　そうだったの
Oh, really?
でもさ “一緒に果たし合いに
行きませんか？”って
But do you think it's normal to say, "Would you come to a duel with me?"
普通 言わないわよ
そんなバカなセリフ
It's such a stupid thing to say.
I'm sure he was just nervous.
きっと焦ってたのよ
可愛いじゃない ダイチ君
Isn't he cute?
（フミエ）
はあ？　何が？　どこが？
What?
What's cute about him?
You really don't get it, do you?
（ヤサコ）フミエちゃん
ホントに分かんないの？
何が？
Get what?
It's so like you.
ホントお似合いよ
Hey, I have an idea!
（ヤサコ）
ねえ 提案があるんだけど
An idea?
（一同）提案？
We still have another thirty minutes before Daichi challenges you again.
（ヤサコ）
ダイチ君が もう一度 申し込むまで
まだ30分あるから
Why don't we walk around?
それまで
ちょっと遊んでいかない？
We are at a festival after all.
せっかくのお祭りよ
Yasako, are you starting to say silly things, too?
ヤサコまで
何 訳分かんないこと言ってんのよ
いいから いいから！
（ダイチ･フミエ）うわっ…
Alright, c'mon!
Ow!
（店主）アイタッ
このガキ どこ狙ってんだ！
Damn brat,
watch where yer aiming!
（ダイチ）すいません
Sorry...
You should try to keep the gun as straight as possible.
（ヤサコ）
できるだけ 銃をまっすぐに…
Man, the tension is so low.
ったく… 緊張感に欠けるぜ
Yeah, Isako is more fit to be a leader than Daichi.
やっぱイサコさんのほうが
オヤビンの器だよね
Right, but I still don't trust that girl.
それはいいが
俺は どうも
あの女 信用できん
Trust?
（イサコ）信用？
（２人）ひぃ…
I don't require your trust.
（イサコ）信用などしなくていいわ
ただ従えばいい
You just need to do as I say.
Isako...
イサコ…
（ナメッチ）…さん？
...san?
What?
（イサコ）何よ どうしたの？
What's wrong?
No, nothing...
（２人）いえいえ なんでも…
Now call those people over for the duel.
さあ 連中に果たし合いを申し込め
Well, actually...
そ… それが
Bad Luck - Don't be Distracted By Little Things and Forget the Big Ones
こ… こんなことではいかん
It's no good!
What's wrong?
（フミエ）どうしたの？
（ダイチ）ちょ… ちょっとトイレ
Um, I have to go to the toilet...
Eh? Hey, Daichi!
あれ？　ダイチ君 どこ行くのよ
Where are you going?
And I...
チェッ せっかく これを…
Here.
（アイコ）はい
（ヤサコ）えっ？
Huh?
Mutual Love
（音楽）
（アイコ）ほら やっぱり！
See?
Just as I thought!
Wh-What?
な… 何よ
It's exactly as I predicted.
私のにらんだとおり
It looks like it'll be easier with you two than Fumie and Daichi.
フミエたちより
こっちが早そうだわ
What are you talking about?
なんのこと？
You're so mean, Aiko!
もうヒドいわ アイコちゃん
Right?
ねえ？
What on earth is he doing?
あいつは何してるのよ
（ダイチ）果たし合い…
A duel...
果たし… 愛
That succeeds...
Hatashiai stands for "duel", but Daichi writes another kanji for "ai" (meet) which can also mean "love".
in love?
（石が当たる音）
（ダイチ）アイテッ！
（イサコ）
ちょっと あんたたち外して
Leave us.
（ガチャギリ･ナメッチ）へい
（イサコ）私ね 呼び出せるの
Listen, I can call her whenever I want.
（ダイチ）何を？
Call who?
（イサコ）ミチコさん
Miss Michiko.
私にはミチコさんを呼び出す
力があるの
I have the power to call Miss Michiko.
そ… それがどうした？
So what?
あいつらのメガネを取り上げるのに
I could call her to help us get those brats' glasses.
ミチコさんの力を
借りてもいいんだけど
あんたがやれば
一番 穏便に片づくわ
But I'd feel better if you did it.
メガネを取り上げれば
あんたの仕事は それで終わり
Your job will be done when you take her glasses.
ありがとう
Thank you.
あっ どこ行ってたのよ
Where have you been?
はい これ
Here, take this.
んっ 100万円
That's one million yen.
（ヤサコ）
いい感じになってきたじゃない
They look much closer now, don't they?
もう一押しね
They just need one more push.
あれ ところでハラケンは？
By the way, where's Haraken?
ちょっと京子をお願い
（アイコ）いいわよ
Could you please take care of Kyoko for a minute?
Okay.
さっきの声 まさか…
The voice I heard...
Could it be?
ねえ ハラケン…
Hey, Harak—
イリーガル？
（ハラケン）シーッ
An Illegal!
うわー 残念
Oh, that was close!
んっ？　どうしたの？
What's wrong?
（フミエ）やっぱ楽しいわ お祭り
You know what? I really like festivals.
ねえ ダイチ 覚えてる？
Hey, Daichi, do you remember?
３年の夏休みに あんた私に
プラチナチケットくれたじゃない
When we were in the third grade,
you offered me a platinum ticket.
一緒に遊んだわよね
こんなふうにさ…
We used to play together like this.
なんか思い出してきちゃった
I suddenly remembered...
あのときは楽しかったな…
It was so much fun back then.
ねえ 次 何やる？
So what shall we do next?
The...
The?
The duel...
（ダイチ）は… 果たし合いを…
We have to duel!
果たし合いをやる！
俺は…
I...
俺は お前なんか…
I really...
hate you!
大っ嫌いだー！
It's heading toward us!
追ってくるわ！　行きましょう
Let's leave!
（イリーガル）ク～ン…
Haraken!
（ヤサコ）ハラケン！
Haraken, it's dangerous!
（ヤサコ）ハラケン 危ないわ！
クロ… クロなのか？
Kuro...
Is it really you, Kuro?
（イリーガル）ク～ン…
待て！
Stop!
クロ…
Kuro...
（ダイチ）
明日からの生物部の合宿で
肝試しをやる
Tomorrow night at the school sleepover,
we'll have a trial of courage.
That will be our duel.
それが果たし合いだ
And what's the prize?
（フミエ）で 何を賭けるの？
Our glasses.
（ダイチ）メガネだ
The loser can't wear glasses over the summer break.
負けたほうは
夏休みの間 メガネを禁止だ
I see it's a serious challenge.
それは重大な勝負ね
The rules are simple.
（ダイチ）ルールは簡単だ
You have to reach the roof safe and sound,
屋上に無事たどり着いて
この人形を置いてくるんだ
and put one of these dolls there.
数の多いほうが勝ちだ
The one who places the most wins.
Th-That'll be a piece of cake.
そ… そんなの楽勝よ
We have a designated path to follow.
（ダイチ）
お互いが指定したコースを行くんだ
We can put as many traps as we like on that path.
コースには
お互いワナを掛け放題だ
I see.
なるほど
I'll put all my best traps.
（ダイチ）せいぜい
ご立派なワナを仕掛けるんだな
I can't wait.
望むところよ
Preview
Next time
on Dennou Coil:
Miss Michiko: From the Other Side.
Miss Michiko
From the Other Side
See you next time!
（ヤサコ）
次回 「電脳コイル」
〝あっちのミチコさん 〞
お楽しみに